Guide to the African American Television Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- African American Television Scripts, (44 boxes)
  - Sanford and Son
    - "Bank On This", 1975 (Box 34)
    - "Brother Can You Spare An Act", 1975 (Box 34)
    - "Camping Trip", 1975 (Box 34)
    - "Can You Chop This?", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "The Director", 1976 (Box 35)
    - "Divorce Sanford Style", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "Donna Pops The Question", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "Earthquake II", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "Ebenezer Sanford", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "The Engagement Man Always Rings Twice", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "The Escorts", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "The Family Man", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "Fred Sanford Has A Baby", 1975 (Box 35)
    - "Fred's Extra Job", 1976 (Box 35)
    - "Fred's Treasure Garden", 1974 (Box 35)
    - "Going Out of Business", 1974 (Box 35)
    - "Golden Boy", 1974 (Box 36)
    - "The Greatest Show In Watts", 1975 (Box 36)
    - "The Headache", 1974 (Box 36)
    - "Home Sweet Home", 1974 (Box 36)
    - "I Dream Of Choo Choo Rabinowitz", 1976 (Box 36)
    - "Julio And Sister and Nephew", 1974 (Box 36)
    - "Lamont In Love", 1975 (Box 36)
    - "A Little Extra Security", 1974 (Box 36)
    - "The Merger", 1974 (Box 36)
    - "My Brother-In-Law's Keeper", 1974 (Box 36)
    - "Ol' Brown Eyes Is Back", 1974 (Box 36)
    - "The Older Woman", 1975 (Box 36)
    - "The Older Woman" (final draft), 1975 (Box 36)
    - "The Olympics", 1975 (Box 36)
    - "Once A Thief", 1974 (Box 37)
    - "The Over-The-Hill Gag", 1975 (Box 37)
    - "A Pain In The Neck", 1976 (Box 37)
    - "Sanford And Niece", 1974 (Box 37)
    - "Sanford And Rising Son", 1975 (Box 37)
    - "Sergeant Gork", 1976 (Box 37)
    - "The Stand-Ins", 1974 (Box 37)
    - "Steinberg And Son", 1975 (Box 37)
    - "Strange Bedfellows", 1974 (Box 37)
    - "The Stung", 1975 (Box 37)
    - "The Surprise Party", 1974 (Box 37)
    - "There'll Be Some Changes Made", 1974 (Box 37)
    - "Tower Power", 1974 (Box 37)
    - "The TV Addict", 1975 (Box 37)
  - Skin Game
    - "Maclendon's People", 1974 (Box 38)
  - Soap
    - Episode 34, 1978 (Box 38)
  - The Sonny And Cher Show
    - Sherman Hemsley, 1976 (Box 38)
  - Strike Force
    - "The Avenger", 1982 (Box 38)
    - "Kiddie Bait", 1981 (Box 38)
    - "Kidnap", 1981 (Box 38)
    - "Magic Man", 1981 (Box 38)
    - "The Predator", 1981 (Box 38)
  - Swiss Family Robinson
    - "The Slave Ship", 1975 (Box 38)
  - That's My Mama
    - "The Ambulance Chaser", 1974 (Box 38)
    - "The Ambulance Chaser" (second draft), 1974 (Box 38)
    - "The Ambulance Chaser" (final draft), 1975 (Box 38)
    - "The Birthday Party", 1975 (Box 39)
    - "The Birthday Party" (final draft), 1975 (Box 39)
    - "Business Is Business", 1975 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton And Politics", 1974 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton And The Kid", 1975 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton Et La Femme", 1975 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton Et La Femme" (second draft), 1975 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton Et La Femme" (final draft), 1975 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton's Big Move", 1974 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton's Big Move" (final draft), 1974 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton's Casual Fling", 1975 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton's Con", 1974 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton's Dubious Romance", 1974 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton's Gun", 1974 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton's Gun" (final draft), 1974 (Box 39)
    - "Clifton's Persuasion", 1974 (Box 40)
    - "Clifton's Sugar Mama", 1974 (Box 40)
    - "Clifton's Sugar Mama" (final draft), 1974 (Box 40)
    - "Cousin Albert", 1974 (Box 40)
    - "Cousin Albert" (final draft), 1974 (Box 40)
    - "A Date With Judy", 1975 (Box 40)
    - "Earl's Dad And Mama's Glad", 1975 (Box 40)
    - "Earl's Dad And Mama's Glad" (second draft), 1975 (Box 40)
    - "Get Your Kicks On Routes 22 And 76", 1975 (Box 40)
    - "The Hero", 1975 (Box 40)
    - "Honesty Day", 1974 (Box 40)
    - "The Image Maker", 1975 (Box 40)
    - "The Last Haircut", 1974 (Box 40)
    - "The Loan", 1974 (Box 40)
    - "Mama Gets Fractured", 1974 (Box 40)
    - "Mama Gets Fractured" (final draft), 1974 (Box 40)
    - "Mama's Big Move", 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Mama's Big Move" (second draft), 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Mama's Big Move" (third draft), 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Mama's Big Move" (fourth draft), 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Mama's Big Move" (final draft), 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Mama's Solution", 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Mama's Solution" (second draft), 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Mama's Solution" (final draft), 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Mama Steps Out", 1974 (Box 41)
    - "A Man From The Past", 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Oscar's Affair", 1974 (Box 41)
    - "Queen Of The Ribs", 1975 (Box 41)
    - "Queen Of The Ribs" (final draft), 1975 (Box 41)
    - "The Shakedown", 1974 (Box 41)
    - "The Shakedown" (final draft), 1974 (Box 41)
    - "Song And Dance Man", 1974 (Box 41)
    - "Stephanie's Boyfriend", 1974 (Box 41)
    - "That's Earl, Brother!", 1975 (Box 42)
    - "That's Earl, Brother!" (second draft), 1975 (Box 42)
    - "That's Earl, Brother!" (final draft), 1975 (Box 42)
    - "Tracy's Trouble", 1974 (Box 42)
    - "Trial And Error", 1975 (Box 42)
    - "Weekend Daddy", 1975 (Box 42)
    - "Weekend Daddy" (second draft), 1975 (Box 42)
    - "Weekend Daddy" (final draft), 1975 (Box 42)
    - "Whose Child Is This?", 1974 (Box 42)
    - "The Witness", 1974 (Box 42)
  - Tony Orlando And Dawn
    Esther Rolle as guest star.
    - Show #4, 1974 (Box 42)
    - Show #4 final draft (Box 42)
  - Waverly Wonders
    - Pilot script, 1978 (Box 42)
    - "Joe Checks Out The Librarian", 1978 (Box 42)
    - "Joe Checks Out The Librarian" (final draft), 1978 (Box 42)
    - "Joe Goes To Press", 1978 (Box 43)
    - "Joe Goes To Press" (final draft), 1978 (Box 43)
    - "The Kiss", 1978 (Box 43)
    - "The Pied Piper", 1978 (Box 43)
    - "The Revolution", 1978 (Box 43)
  - Webster
    - "Rich Man, Poor Man", 1988 (Box 44)
  - Welcome Back, Kotter
    - Untitled pilot script, 1975 (Box 44)
    - "Arrivederci, Arnold", 1975 (Box 44)
    - "Classroom Marriage", 1975 (Box 44)
    - "Classroom Marriage" (final draft), 1975 (Box 44)
    - "The Election", 1975 (Box 44)
    - "Father Vinnie", 1976 (Box 44)
    - "The Great Debate", 1975 (Box 44)
    - "Mr Kotter, Teacher", 1975 (Box 44)
    - "No More Mr. Nice Guy", 1975 (Box 44)
    - "One Flu Over The Cuckoo's Nest", 1976 (Box 44)
    - "One Of Our Sweathogs Is Missing", 1975 (Box 44)
    - "The Reunion", 1975 (Box 44)
    - "Whodunit?", 1975 (Box 44)
  - What's Happening Now
    - "Rags To Riches", 1985 (Box 44)
  - The Young Lawyers
    - "Six To Ten On Sunday After The Game", 1971 (Box 44)
    - "The Sorrow At Sargent's Wharf", 1970 (Box 44)